Guide to the Bureau of Applied Social Research records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- X: Center for the Social Sciences
  - Materials relating to the Center's Winter 1982 Newsletter, Volume 2, No. 3, 1981-1982 (Box 163)
  - Materials related to the Center's Spring 1982 Newsletter, 1982 (?) (Box 163)
  - Correspondence and articles on stress for the Fall 1983 Newsletter, 1983, 1983 (?) (Box 163)
  - Final Proof Copies of Fall 1983 Newsletter, Vol.3, No.2,1983, 1983 (?) (Box 163)
  - Materials Relating to the Center's Spring 1984 Newsletter, (1980's?) (Box 163)
  - Final Manuscripts and Attached Correspondence for Spring 1984 Newsletter, (1980's?) (Box 163)
  - Typescript: Code Book for Finance Agencies Study of comptrollers offices and Departments of Finance in the United States, No Date (1980's?), (pp.1-78 Blue Bound Xerox Copy) (Box 163)
- XI: Card Catalog of BASR Library
  - Card Catalog, Articles, miscellaneous and A-H in six smaller grey boxes (Box 164)
  - Card Catalog, I - Z in six smaller grey boxes. (Box 165)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul F. Social Research in Poland, February, 1968, (Cover sheet, plus 22 pages ) (Box 59, Folder F-0640)
  - Benefits, Incomes and Expenditures of Unemployed Workers: A Procedural Report. A. J. Jaffe and Jeanne Bilby, 1958, ( 79 pp. ) (Box 125, Folder B-0573-1)
    [This is a description and evaluation of a survey of unemployment beneficiaries in Albany-Schenectady-Troy, N.Y., in 1957. Questionnaire included. Main concern is how well benefits are able to meet workers' needs, particularly non-deferrable ones. REPORT NOT AVAILABLE]
  - Mitchell, Robert E. "Polity, Church Attractiveness, and Ministers' Careers: An Eight-Denomination Study of Interchurch Mobility." Journal for the Scientific Study of Religion, Spring, 1966, (pp. 241-258. ) (Box 139, Folder A 397)